What the hell is this?!
That bastard. Why'd he send us here?!
Hey, there were apparently fireworks
going off until a second ago.
minutes
Plus, this park is right
next to a train station.
Let's split into two groups!
You guys search the other end!
This must be the place.
Please walk in a straight line.
Dammit! Too many people!
There's going to be a rush of people
going home from a fireworks display.
Which is great for buying time.
They'll have to split up to find me.
Were you even listening?!
I told you, you gotta do this
without getting caught!
And I will.
They'll probably all show
up inside of ten minutes.
And then—
Pedestrian
Heaven
That's a lotta people.
Is this seriously gonna work?
You can come by if you want, but I'm
begging you, try and stay hidden.
I know well enough to do that
without him tellin' me.
Move!
There he is...
Man, and this skirt was expensive!
Dammit!
To Be Honest, I Want to Marry You
Part Two
Hey, get out of the way!
Damn, this is annoying!
If we keep moving this way, we're just
gonna run into the other group.
Hey! Make sure to check all
the little side paths, too!
R-Right!
How the hell are we supposed to
find some guy we barely know?
Quit complaining or they'll kill you too.
I'd like to see them try!
Who's there?!
You...
Hands up.
I only want to hear answers
to my questions.
Say anything else and I'll make it so you
won't be eating solid food ever again.
Got it?
How many are left, other than you two?
Hey!
What the hell do you guys
think you're doing?!
Shut up and fuck off, or you're dead.
A-Are you stupid or something?!
Waltzing right into a
spot that he specified?
This is why I hate working
with idiots like you!
Yo, you guys go on without me.
I'm gonna take care of him first.
Let go! Dammit.... you asshole!
Do you know what's going
to happen if you hurt me?!
Azami-san won't let it slide!
Azami? That dude's just
a yakuza bottom-feeder.
Do you seriously believe that?
What the hell are you yapping about now?
If he were a typical yakuza,
he wouldn't be looking after you clowns,
no matter how much cash you bring in.
A year ago, some of the Katabami-kai's
people came to shake down my business.
And you need yakuza to
solve yakuza problems.
The problem is it costs an arm and a leg.
Right when I was worried about my dad getting
on my case about having beef with yakuza,
he reached out to me.
"He"?
I hadn't mentioned what was going
on to anyone, but he knew.
He approached me like he was
just your average student.
Are you Ozu Kento?
Want me to take care of it?
I have no idea how he heard about it...
Which creeped me out, so I told
him to go ahead, if he could.
And in under a week...
Not just the guys who came after me...
The other members and even
their boss just went missing.
Not confirmed dead, mind you. Just vanished.
No telling whether or not
they're alive anymore.
Who's he talking about?
Dammit, what's Kirishima doing?!
After that, a year passed
without a word from him.
No offers to do any more favors,
and he didn't hit me up for any money.
I did my best to figure out who he was,
but couldn't turn up anything.
Then after all this time, he shows up.
Says he wants a favor.
Guys like him are seriously scary.
The ones who won't shut up about money
and chicks are way more trustworthy.
He's not anything like that.
He's not footing the bill for you punks
out of the goodness of his heart.
He's just using you like pawns!
The fuck's it matter, dickhead?
Hey, you. Get out here, now.
Where the hell are you bastards?!
Well... we found him.
Miyama Kirishima.
He's in the public bathroom over
towards the entrance to the station.
Where's the guy who was with you?
Oh... Kirishima got him.
Right now, I'm hiding.
You're not alone, are you?
I guess you're not that stupid, huh?
You asshole!
He's not lying, though.
I can send you my location info if you want.
What do you think you're doing?!
It takes too much effort to
hunt you down individually.
And there's really only one
route through this park.
So I'm going to wait right here.
I believe it's Ozu Kento
and Naoya-san, right?
Would you mind bringing the
two of them over to me?
I believe they are, technically, in charge.
It's tiring, you know?
Having to clean up a bunch of scum that
were scraped together out of nowhere.
Do you guys honestly not realize how bad
an idea it is to pick a fight with me yet?
You were making some decent
dirty money with Akaza Shiori,
and then she was forced to flee overseas.
Yet you guys get to stay in Japan.
Didn't you ever wonder why?
Because I let you.
I can understand why you'd be grateful,
but I'm baffled at this beef you have.
Who the fuck do you think
you are, you little shit?!
You don't have a single clue
about what's going on, do you?
No, you don't.
Now stop running your
mouth and get over here.
I don't have any more time
to waste on the help.
You get in touch with Naoya?
No. Not Ozu, either.
What do we do? Something
might have happened to them.
Doesn't matter.
The asshole's by himself.
Contact everyone who's out searching!
And once we have him, I'll kill him myself.
Wh-What are you going to—
Hey! I know you heard me!
Quit snooping around!
He knows I'm here!
You wanna kill me too, right,
Miyama Kirishima?!
And he don't even realize it's me!
Am I too far away?
Get out here right now!
Hey, it's been a while.
I was wonderin' what you guys
were doin' here in Osaka...
But Kirishima's not here.
You dumb bitch.
I've got business with you, too.
I don't care how much of a
big shot your grandpa is,
you screwed with the wrong guy!
I'm not gonna make it easy, either.
After Miyama Kirishima's beaten to a pulp,
we're gonna pass you around before
killing you in front of him.
What the hell? You seriously
don't have a clue.
All that'd do is make him happy.
Dude's a total masochist.
Honestly, the fact that I was even
able to find you means you screwed up.
Your whole crew has no
idea what they're doing.
Or did you come to Osaka
to sample our hospitals?
'Cuz it seems like you just don't learn.
Bitch!
Who do you think you are?!
What happened?
Is it a blackout?
Die.
Kirishima?
Get back here!
What's going on?
Talk about annoying.
Dammit, the power's out.
Hang on a sec.
Hey, what the hell's going on?
I'm telling you guys not to move!
Miyama Kirishima is pulling something.
Check and make sure you're all there!
What was that just now?
Dammit!
Hey? Hey!
Shit! All of you, surround him!
Hey, what's going on?
Everyone in front is down!
He's coming!
Shit! I can't see anything!
Hey, did someone just fall over?
Hey, quit pushing.
Where the hell is he?!
Bastard!
Asshole! You...
Y-You...
You... piece of shit!
Hey there. I'm lucky he was
the last of them.
Ow...
Hey, my tooth came out!
That piece of shit... better put it back.
Out of the way!
Aw, crap.
What do I do? Go to the police box?
Nah, not after I picked a
fight with him. Too lame.
What's around here, anyway?
Anything I can use?
Public Parking
Left turn in 300 meters
Bike Rentals
It's nice to meet you.
You must be the one behind this harassment
campaign I've been dealing with.
It's kind of a pain to have it follow
me all the way to Osaka, you know.
I feel guilty saying this, considering
how much work you must've gone through,
but I honestly can't really narrow down
what might this might be about.
What do you want?
Where's Somei Yoshino?
You seriously went to all this trouble,
and it's just the girl you're after?
I heard that she was always with you.
But I guess not.
I'll leave you to it, then.
You can find girls like her anywhere.
She's not that remarkable,
apart from her face and body.
How about I introduce you to someone else?
I have business with Somei Yoshino.
Well, that's a problem.
I don't see how...
If she's the kind of girl you can
find anywhere, like you just said.
There's obviously no one else like her!
You're...
Suo Azami?!
How deep in this are you?
Actually, now that I think about it—
When did you get that face?
Finally, some light!
Whoa... are those people on the ground?
Was there a fight?
What now?
Your friends are scattered around the park.
You should probably collect them
and leave before the cops show up.
Or maybe you'd rather we keep
going until one of us dies.
Bored now.
You're all totally useless.
There was no point in me coming
if I couldn't see her.
Tell Somei Yoshino I said hi.
You sure about this?
Wouldn't it be better for you if I was dead?
You think you're a big deal, don't you?
These bottom-feeding punks are the
only ones who care about you.
I don't have time to waste
on you. Not right now.
Hey, move!
Out of the way, dammit!
Thank you for your patronage.
You have reserved: 30 minutes.
Your service period will not
begin until you retrieve your bicycle.
Okay, all set!
Move!
Shit!
Rental Cycle
Hey! You talk all that shit
and now you're hiding?!
Dead End Ahead
Okay, bitch, I'll give you a chance.
Bring Miyama Kirishima here...
And I'll let you go.
Understand? This is your last—
Hey, on your right!
Come on, right, right, right!
Look at me! Right here!
Aw, shit, my back...
You... bitch...
Sorry!
Looks like you're headed for the
hospital again, after all.
Karaoke Albatross
You're a sturdy bastard, huh?
You're from Tokyo, ain't you?
What're you doin' in Osaka?
I'm not technically from Tokyo.
What is it about yakuza that makes you
think of everything in terms of turf?
You son of a...
Are you kidding me?!
Pause, time out.
Dammit! And he's not picking up!
All this, and now we're going home?!
He's got no concept of teamwork!
We're done, beanpole.
But if you call me curly again,
you're dead meat, for real.
Seriously, who the hell are you anyway?
I wanna be reimbursed for this suit.
Hold up. What's your business
with Miyama Kirishima?
Man, I don't have business with him.
You seriously think I'd come all the
way to Osaka to help a bunch of goons
I don't even know with their revenge?
This is work for me.
You're Kirigaya-gumi, right?
And low enough on the ladder that
you don't know what's going on.
What're you gettin' at?
There's gonna be a lot of tedious
internal beef down the line.
If I were you, I'd quit being
a yakuza while I could.
Miyama Kirishima's a part of it.
Shit.
You okay, Ozu-kun?
Let's pick up where we left off.
Got plenty to talk about while we drink.